#### Contact

amol.bhadane999@gmail.com 9970067477 Linkodla Profile

### Network

Amol knows 1 person at your company

Top Skills · See all

Social Media Marketing · Search
Engine Optimization (SEO)
· Google Adwords · Google
Analytics · Mobile Marketing ·
Email Marketing · WordPress
· Digital Marketing · Digital
Strategy · Online Marketing

Accomplishments · See all

4 Certifications · 3 Languages

Recommendations · See all

Jayesh Shelar Software Engineer at Aress Software

Arpitha Prakash
Graphic Designer at INKONIQ

# **Amol Bhadane**

sr. Digital Marketing Analyst at pinclick Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

## Summary

Pursued Training in Digital Marketing from Web Marketing Academy (WMA), Bangalore for 4 months Dec 2016 – Apr 2017 Extensive learning on Search Engine Optimization which includes keyword research and optimization, site audit and getting knowhow of various tools like RAVEN, SPYFU, Keywordtool. io, Keyword planner. Learnt how to write SEO friendly content. Performed a comp...

## Experience

Sr.Digital Marketing Analyst · Pin Click June 2018 - Present · Bangalore

Digital Marketing Specialist (Freelancer) · Namdhari's Fresh January 2018 - June 2018 (6 months) · Bengaluru Area, India

Digital Marketing Analyst · Lensinteractive August 2017 - April 2018 (9 months) · India

Digital Marketing Specialist (Freelancer) · Haqeeba December 2016 - August 2017 (9 months)

#### Education

Karnataka State Open University

Master of Business Administration, Marketing (2014 - 2017)